Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Job 581, Frankfort, Blue – line Drawings,1982 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Job 581, Frankfort, Photographs,1982-1983 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Job 582, Sheboygan, WI,1981-1984 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Job 582, Sheboygan, WI, Contract and Estimate,1982 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Job 582, Sheboygan, WI, Correspondence,1982-1983 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Job 582, Sheboygan, WI, Drawings,1983 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Job 582, Sheboygan, WI, Photographs,undated (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Job 582, Sheboygan, WI, Progressive Fabricators Inc. Correspondence1982-1983 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Job 583, Lakewood, OH,1982 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Job 584, Frankfort,1982-1983 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Job 584, Frankfort, Drawings,1982 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Job 585, Lorain, OH,1982 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Job, 586, Catawba, OH,1982 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Job, 586, Catawba, OH, Bid,1982 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Job, 586, Catawba, OH, Drawings,1982 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Job 587, Lorain, OH,1983 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Job 587, Lorain, OH, Bid, Estimate and Contract,1983 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Job 588, Toledo, OH,1983 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Job 588, Toledo, OH, Contract and Estimate,1983 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Job 588, Toledo, OH, Drawings,1983 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Job 589, Milwaukee, WI,1983 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH,1982 – 1984 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Bid,1983 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Contract Correspondence,1983-1985 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Correspondence,1983 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Correspondence,January – July, 1984 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Correspondence,August – December, 1984 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Correspondence,1985 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Drawings and Maps,1983 – 1984 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Estimate,1983 – 1985 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Feick Contractors Correspondence,1984 – 1985 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Receipts, 1 of 2,1983 – 1985 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Job 590, Sandusky, OH, Receipts, 2 of 2,1983 – 1985 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Job 591, Harrisville,1983 – 1984 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Job 591, Harrisville, Bid and Estimate,1983 – 1985 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Job 591, Harrisville, Drawings,1983 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Job 591, Harrisville, Photographs,1984 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Job 592, South Manitou Island,1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Job 592, South Manitou Island, Contract and Estimate,1983 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Job 592, South Manitou Island, Photographs,1983 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Job 593, Milwaukee, WI,1983 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Job 593, Milwaukee, WI, Bid, Contract and Estimate,1983 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Job 593, Milwaukee, WI, Bid, Correspondence,1983 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Job 594, Dunkirk, NY,1983 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Job 595, Mouillee,1983-1984 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Job 595, Mouillee, Bid, Estimate and Contract,1983 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Job 595, Mouillee, Drawings,1983 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Job 596, Lake City, MN,1983-1984 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Job 596, Lake City, MN, Contract,1983-1984 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Job 596, Lake City, MN, Correspondence,1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Job 596, Lake City, MN, Estimate,1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Job 596, Lake City, MN, Receipts,1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Job 596, Lake City, MN, Specifications,1983 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Job 597, Lansing, IA,1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Job 597, Lansing, IA, Contract,1983 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Job 597, Lansing, IA, Correspondence,1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Job 597, Lansing, IA, Estimate,1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Job 597, Lansing, IA, Plans and Specifications,1983 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Job 597, Lansing, IA, Receipts,1983-1984 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Job 598, Frankfort,1983 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Job 599, Toledo, OH,1983 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Job 599, Toledo, OH, Contracts,1983 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Job 599, Toledo, OH, Estimate and Receipts,1983 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Job 599, Toledo, OH, Plans and Specifications,1984 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Job 600, Chicago, IL,1984 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Job 600, Chicago, IL, Blue - line Drawings,1984 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Job 600, Chicago, IL, Contract,1984 (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Job 600, Chicago, IL, Correspondence,1984 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Job 600, Chicago, IL, Estimate,1984 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Job 600, Chicago, IL, Specifications,1984 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Job 601, Frankfort,1984 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Job 602, St. Joseph,1984 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Job 602, St. Joseph, Blue – line Drawings,1984 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Job 602, St. Joseph, Contract,1984 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Job 602, St. Joseph, Correspondence,1984 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Job 602, St. Joseph, Estimate,1984 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Job 602, St. Joseph, Specifications,1984 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Job 603, Milwaukee, WI,1984 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Job 603, Milwaukee, WI, Estimate and Receipts,1984 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Job 604, Frankfort,1984 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Job 605, Ashtabula, OH,1984 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Job 605, Ashtabula, OH, Drawings,1984 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Job 606, Green Bay, WI,1984 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Job 606, Green Bay, WI, Bid and Estimate,1984 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Job 606, Green Bay, WI, Drawings,1984 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Job 607, Calumet, IL,1984 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Job 607, Calumet, IL, Bid and Estimate,1984 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Job 607, Calumet, IL, Drawings,1984 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Job 607, Calumet, IL, Specifications,1984 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY,1984-1986 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Bid Invitation,1984 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Claim #1, 1 of 2,1985-1986 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Claim #1, 2 of 2,1985-1986 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Claim #1, Backup Information,1985-1986 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Claim #2,1986-1987 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Claim #2, Backup Information,1986-1987 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Contract,1984 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Contract Correspondence,1984-1986 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Contract Modifications,1984 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Correspondence,1984 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Correspondence,1985 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Correspondence,1986-1987 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Drawings, 1 of 2,1984-1986 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Drawings, 2 of 2,1984-1986 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Estimate,1984-1986 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Negatives,1984 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Newspaper Clippings,1984-1986 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Newspaper Clippings,Undated (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Orders,1984-1986 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Payment Estimates,1984-1987 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Photographs,1984-1985 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Protest Signs,1985 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Job 608, Irondequoit, NY, Specifications,1985 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Job 609, Sheboygan, WI,1984 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Job 609, Sheboygan, WI, Blue – line Drawings,1984 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Job 609, Sheboygan, WI, Receipts,1984 (Box 216, Folder 12)
  - Job 610, Alton, IL,1984 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Job 610, Alton, IL, Blue – line Drawings,1984 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Job 610, Alton, IL, Contract,1984 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Job 610, Alton, IL, Estimate,1984 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Job 610, Alton, IL, Receipts,1984 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Job 610, Alton, IL, Specifications,1984 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY,1984 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Blue – line Drawings,1984 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Canonie Transportation Correspondence, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Canonie Transportation Correspondence, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Canonie Transportation Correspondence, List of Exhibits,1984 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Contract,1984 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Correspondence,1984 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Estimate and Receipts,1984 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Job 611, Barcelona, NY, Orders,1984 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Job 612, Milwaukee, WI,1986 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Job 613, Fairport, OH,1984 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Job 614, Ogdensburg, NY,1984-1985 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Job 614, Ogdensburg, NY, Blue – line Drawings,1984 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Job 614, Ogdensburg, NY, Contract,1984-1985 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Job 615, Muskegon,1984-1987 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Bethlehem Steel Correspondence,1985 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Contract Correspondence,1984-1988 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Contract Modifications, 1 of 2,1984-1987 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Contract Modifications, 2 of 2,1984-1987 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Correspondence, 1 of 3,1984-1987 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Correspondence, 2 of 3,1984-1987 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Correspondence, 3 of 3,1984-1987 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Estimate,1984-1988 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Orders, 1 of 2,1984-1986 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Orders, 2 of 2,1984-1986 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Payment Estimate, 1 of 2,1984-1987 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Payment Estimate, 2 of 2,1984-1987 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Photographs,1985 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Quality Assurance Reports,1985 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Job 615, Muskegon, Specifications,1984 (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Job 617, Manitowoc, WI,1984 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Job 618, Hammond, IN,1985 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Job 618, Hammond, IN, Receipts, Contract and Estimate,1985 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Job 618, Hammond, IN, Specifications and Drawings,1985 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Job 619, Holland,1985 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Job 619, Holland, Bid,1985 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Job 619, Holland, Blue – line Drawings,1985 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Job 619, Holland, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1985 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Job 620, Grand Haven,1985 (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - Job 620, Grand Haven, Bid,1985 (Box 222, Folder 10)
  - Job 620, Grand Haven, Contract, Receipts, and Estimate,1985 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Job 620, Grand Haven, Marine Accidents, 1 of 2,1985 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Job 620, Grand Haven, Marine Accidents, 2 of 2,1985 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Job 621, Alpena,1985 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Job 621, Alpena, Bid,1985 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Job 621, Alpena, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1985 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Job 621, Alpena, Drawings,1985 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Job 622, Chicago, IL,1985 (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Job 622, Chicago, IL, Bid,1985 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Job 622, Chicago, IL, Contract, Receipts, and Estimate,1985 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Job 622, Chicago, IL, Drawings,1985 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Job 623, Frankfort,1985 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Job 623, Frankfort, Drawings,1985 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Job 624, Au Gres,1985 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Bid, Estimate and Orders,1985 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Blue – line Drawings,1985 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Contract Correspondence,1985 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1985 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1985 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Drawings,1985 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Receipts,1985 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Yacht Club Correspondence, 1 of 3,1987-1992 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Yacht Club Correspondence, 2 of 3,1987-1992 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Job 624, Au Gres, Yacht Club Correspondence, 3 of 3,1987-1992 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Job 625, Ontonagon,1985 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Job 625, Ontonagon, Bid,1985 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Job 625, Ontonagon, Contract, Receipts and Estimate,1985 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Job 626, Holland,1985 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Job 627, Waukegan, IL,1985 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - Job 627, Waukegan, IL, Contract Correspondence,1985 (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Job 627, Waukegan, IL, Specifications and Blue – line Drawings,1985 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH,1985 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Bid and Estimate,1985 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Claims, 1 of 2,1985-1987 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Claims, 2 of 2,1985-1987 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Contract Correspondence,1986-1987 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Correspondence, 1 of 3,1986-1987 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Correspondence, 2 of 3,1986-1987 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Correspondence, 3 of 3,1986-1987 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Drawings,1984-1986 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Orders and Receipts,1986 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Price Brothers Correspondence,1986-1988 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Job 628, Lorain, OH, Specifications,1984 – 1985 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Job 629, Green Bay, WI,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Job 629, Green Bay, WI, Contract, 1 of 2,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Job 629, Green Bay, WI, Contract, 2 of 2,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Job 629, Green Bay, WI, Contract Performance,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Job 630, White Lake,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Job 630, White Lake, Contract,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Job 630, White Lake, Drawings,1985 – 1986 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Job 631, Frankfort,1985 – 1986 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Job 632, Frankfort,1986 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Job 633, Green Bay, WI,1985-1986 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI,1985-1987 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Bid and Estimate,1986 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Claim, 1 of 2,1986 – 1989 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Claim, 2 of 2,1986 – 1989 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1986 – 1987 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1986 – 1987 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Contract,1985 – 1986 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Drawings,1986 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Negatives,Undated (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Newspaper Clippings,1986 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Photographs,1986 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Schooner Rosabelle History,1986 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Job 634, Racine, WI, Specifications,1985 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Job 635, Manistee,1986 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Job 635, Manistee, Bid,1986 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Job 635, Manistee, Contract, Estimate and Receipts,1986 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Job 635, Manistee, Drawings,1986 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH,1986 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Contract, Orders and Receipts,1986 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Specifications, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Job 636, Toledo, OH, Specifications, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Job 637, Arcadia,1986 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Contract, Orders and Receipts,1986 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Drawings,1986 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Job 637, Arcadia, Estimate,1986 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Job 638, Manistee,1986 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Job 638, Manistee, Bid and Estimate,1986 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Job 638, Manistee, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Job 638, Manistee, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Job 638, Manistee, Contract Correspondence,1986-1987 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Job 638, Manistee, Orders and Receipts,1986-1987 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH,1986 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Contract,1986 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Correspondence, 1 of 3,1986 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Correspondence, 2 of 3,1986 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Correspondence, 3 of 3,1986 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Estimate,1986 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Orders, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Orders, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Photographs,1986 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Job 639, Cleveland, OH, Specifications,1986 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH,1986-1987 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Bid,1986 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Blue – line Drawings,1986 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Contract,1986 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Correspondence, 1 of 2,1986-1987 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Correspondence, 2 of 2,1986-1987 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Estimate,1986 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Job 640, Lorain, OH, Orders and Receipts,1986 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY,1986-1987 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Bid,1986 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Claim, Hillyer and Irwin, 1 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Claim, Hillyer and Irwin, 2 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Claim, Hillyer and Irwin, 3 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Claim, Hillyer and Irwin, 4 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Contract, Orders and Receipts,1986 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Correspondence and Estimate,1986-1987 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, Drawings,1986 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Job 641, Buffalo, NY, List of Exhibits,1987 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Appendix A, 1 of 3,1997 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Appendix A, 2 of 3,1997 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Appendix A, 3 of 3,1997 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Correspondence,1988-1991 (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Documents,1997 (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Response, Volume 1 of 2,1997 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Job 642, U.S. District Court vs. Luedtke, Response, Volume 2 of 2,1997 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island,1986-1987 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Bid,1986 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Claim and Estimate,1987-1988 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Contract,1987 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Correspondence,1986-1987 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, List of Exhibits,1988 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Orders and Receipts,1986-1987 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Job 643, Grassy Island, Photographs,1986-1987 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI,1986-1987 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Bid and Estimate,1986-1987 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Contract,1986-1987 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Drawings,1986-1987 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Photographs,undated (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Prepakt Concrete Correspondence,1986 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Negatives,undated (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Newspaper Clippings,1986 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Photographs of Interest,1986 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Specifications,undated (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Job 644, Milwaukee, WI, Tug and Barge Rental,1987 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Job 645, Frankfort,1986-1987 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Job 646, Frankfort,1987-1988 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Job 647, Kewaunee, WI,1987 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Job 648, Arcadia,1987 (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Job 649, Manitou Island,1986-1987 (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Job 649, Manitou Island, Blue – line Drawings,1986-1987 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Job 650, Harrisville,1987 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Job 651, Saginaw, 1 of 2,1987-1988 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Job 651, Saginaw, 2 of 2,1987-1988 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Job 651, Saginaw, Contract,1987 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Job 652, Allendale,1987-1988 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Job 652, Allendale, Contract,1987 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Job 653, Avon Lake, OH,1987 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Job 653, Avon Lake, OH, Contract,1987 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Job 653, Avon Lake, OH, Drawings,1987 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Job 653, Avon Lake, OH, Photographs,undated (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Job 654, Elberta,1987-1988 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Job 655, Cleveland, OH,1987 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Job 656, Lakeside Marblehead, OH,1987 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Job 656, Lakeside Marblehead, OH, Contract,1987 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI,1987 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Bid,1987 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Blue – line Drawings,1987-1988 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Claim, 1 of 4,1987-1989 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Claim, 2 of 4,1987-1989 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Claim, 3 of 4,1987-1989 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Claim, 4 of 4,1987-1989 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Correspondence, 1 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Correspondence, 2 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Correspondence, 3 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Correspondence, 4 of 4,1987-1988 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Equitable Adjustment Claim,1988 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Equitable Adjustment Claim Correspondence, 1 of 2,1987-1988 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Job 657, Green Bay, WI, Equitable Adjustment Claim Correspondence, 2 of 2,1987-1988 (Box 249, Folder 5)